So far in this lesson,
到目前为止
you've learned how to use
你已经学习了
optimization techniques to come up with optimal portfolio weights.
如何利用优化技巧得出最优投资组合权重
Is your job done? Not really.
任务完成了吗？并没有
As a portfolio manager,
作为投资组合经理
the next step after portfolio construction,
构建投资组合后的下一步是
is to constantly monitor your portfolio,
时刻监控投资组合
and make sure it is in line with your goals.
确保它与目标保持一致
Over time, assets produce returns that can differ from those originally estimated.
随着时间的推移 资产的收益率可能与一开始估算的有差别
So, the amount of money invested in different assets, changes.
投资到不同资产的金额会变化
Therefore, the portfolio weights,
所以代表投资到
which represent the proportion of money invested in each asset, change.
每个资产的金额所占比例的权重会变化
In order to make sure the portfolio maintains the desired set of weights,
为了使投资组合保持期望的权重
we need two rebalance.
我们需要再平衡
For example, say we started with a strategy in which we wanted to invest
例如 一开始我们的策略是
50% of our portfolio in a solar energy company and 50% in a construction company.
向太阳能公司投入 50% 的资金 并向建筑公司投入 50% 的资金
Let's say the solar energy company does really well
假设太阳能公司的业绩很好
and it's value appreciates such that the shares we've invested in it,
它的市值上涨了 使我们投入的股票价值
now represent 70% of the value of our portfolio.
代表了投资组合 70% 的价值
If we wanted to return to the 50% in
如果要使
a solar energy company and 50% in the construction company,
太阳能公司和建筑公司保持 50-50 比例
we'd sell some shares of the solar energy company,
我们需要出售一些太阳能公司股票
and buy some shares of the construction company to bring us back to 50-50.
并买入一些建筑公司股票 才能回到 50-50 比例
When you have determined your portfolio weights
通过优化方法确定投资组合权重后
via optimization and later want to rebalance,
日后想再平衡投资组合的话
you simply re-run the optimization with the same objective function and constraints,
只需使用相同的目标函数和约束条件重新优化即可
but using updated data.
但需要使用更新后的数据
Before we discuss different rebalancing strategies,
在讨论不同的再平衡策略之前
let's consider the costs incurred during rebalancing.
我们考虑下再平衡过程中产生的成本
Think about it, when you rebalance, you place trades.
再平衡需要交易
To place trades, you generally have to pay a broker commissions.
交易通常需要支付佣金
These commissions are one type of transaction costs.
这些佣金是一种交易成本
Transaction costs, are probably the most important costs incurred during rebalancing.
交易成本是再平衡过程中最重要的成本
But, there are others, such as taxes,
还有其他成本 例如资本利得税等税收
like capital gains taxes and the administrative costs of time and labor.
还有时间和人力管理成本
Transaction costs can be potentially significant.
交易成本可能很高
In the year 2000,
在 2000 年
the Texas Permanent School Fund rebalanced its portfolio of
Texas Permanent School Fund 再平衡了
more than 2,000 securities, 40 portfolio managers,
超过 2,000 支证券 涉及 40 名投资组合经理
500 million shares, and $17.5 billion were involved not including administrative costs,
5 亿股票以及 175 亿美元 这还不包括管理成本
the transactions themselves costs $120 million.
交易本身的成本是 1.2 亿美元
Now, you can see how crazy transaction costs can be.
现在你可以看出交易成本有多高了
In general, it's hard to model transaction costs directly.
通常 很难直接衡量交易成本
To know the transaction costs,
要知道交易成本
you must know what the trade is.
必须知道交易是什么
But the whole reason to do the optimization,
但是进行优化的原因就是
is to know what the trade is.
要知道交易是什么
So, instead of trying to estimate transaction costs,
与其估算交易成本
we can make the assumption that transaction costs will be
我们将假设交易成本
proportional to the magnitude of change in the holdings.
与持有量变化大小成比例
This is called portfolio turnover and it's basically,
称为投资组合周转率
the sum total of the changes in the weights on all the assets.
等于所有资产权重的变化总和
To calculate turnover between two time periods,
为了计算两个时期之间的周转率
you would take the absolute value of
需要计算每个资产
the difference in weight between two time periods for each asset,
在两个时期之间的权重差异绝对值
and then sum these over assets.
然后对这些绝对值求和
To get an annualized turnover,
为了计算年化周转率
you would calculate the average turnover per rebalancing event by calculating,
需要计算每个再平衡事件的平均周转率
total turnover for all the rebalancing events in the timeframe you're considering,
公式为用相关时期内的所有再平衡事件的总周转率
and dividing by the number of rebalancing events,
除以再平衡事件数量
and then multiplying by the number of rebalancing events per year.
然后乘以每年的再平衡事件数量